cland.io 2018-09-01

# Privacy Policy - CLAND | EDM Community

This CLAND.IO Privacy Policy, in conjunction with the AUP, Terms of Service and other terms and conditions of use which are incorporated herein by reference and may be posted and applicable to specific services, governs your use of the CLAND.IO website and are collectively referred to as the "Agreement". Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available in our footer and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

CLAND.IO may modify the Agreement which will become effective immediately upon posting on the website. Your continued use of the website and any associated services, the "Services", indicates your acceptance of the Agreement.

Any Content posted by you to CLAND.IO becomes published Content and is not considered personally identifiable information subject to this Privacy Policy.

CLAND.IO uses IP addresses to measure usage and analyze trends, administer the website and collect information for its databases.

We will not rent, sell or share your information with third parties. However, we may disclose your personal information or any of its log file information when required by law or in the good-faith belief that such actions are necessary to: conform to the edicts of the law or comply with a legal process served on us; protect and defend the rights or property of CLAND.IO, or visitors of CLAND.IO; identify persons who may be violating the law, the legal notice, or the rights of third parties; co-operate with the investigations of purported unlawful activities.

Third-party websites linked to CLAND.IO are not covered by this Privacy Policy. These websites may collect personally identifiable information about you and place a cookie on your browser. CLAND.IO is not responsible for the privacy practices of the third-party websites and companies.

CLAND.IO is not responsible if you volunteer personal information online that is accessible to the public. You may receive unsolicited messages from other parties or it may be used in a manner that violates the law, your personal privacy or your safety. By submitting such information, you assume the risks and sole liability arising as a result of such information being displayed.

If you are not a resident of the Cyprus, you understand and agree that CLAND.IO stores and processes your information on computers located in the Cyprus, any by providing any data to CLAND.IO, you consent to the transfer of such information to Cyprus.

In the event that CLAND.IO is acquired or merged with a third party entity, we reserve the right to transfer or assign the information we have collected from you as part of any change of control. In the unlikely event of our bankruptcy, insolvency, reorganization, receivership, or assignment for the benefit of creditors, or the application of laws or equitable principles affecting creditors' rights generally, CLAND.IO may not be able to control how your personal information is treated, transferred or used.

Although we strive to protect your personal information, CLAND.IO cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk.

Log files are maintained and analysed of all requests for files on this website's web servers. Log files do not capture personal information but do capture the user's IP address, which is automatically recognised by our web servers.

**Our Commitment to Children's Privacy**  
Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.

**Cookies**  
This website does not store any information that would, on its own, allow us to identify individual users of this service without their permission. Any cookies that may be used by this website are used either solely on a per session basis or to maintain user preferences. Cookies are not shared with any third parties.
